I usually wear size small but this time I had to order size extra large.
Let's talk about Asian sizing today because I was not prepared for this and
was humbled real quick. Of course I'm used to it by now Asian sizing but the
first time I ordered it I was so confused. I was like I'm wearing size
large or extra large? It can't be and yeah my ego left a chat with that and I
also get a lot of comments still from people who are confused by which size to order because Asian
sizing is different than European sizing and you have to be really really careful and you have to
check the size chart and compare the measurements of the size chart to what you need and not to the
size you're used to. So why is Asian sizing different? That's because body proportions are
different over in Asia compared to Europe they like their clothes tighter they're smaller per se
so I am as a tall person really have trouble to find things that are long enough for me because
they're just not cut for this market for the European one and I can also wear size large
with Amoresi but if I want to have a really comfortable experience then I'll use the extra
Lodge and I had to get used to that and there's no shame in that this is just a letter on a label
I love this new design and I have it in a second color so I'm going to change and meanwhile you
can check out the discount code I have for Amorisi in the description text now my top tips for
ordering clothes with Asian sizing check the measurement chart and if the manufacturer does
not provide one, write an email and ask them. Or check the customer feedback and the reviews.
Usually people write down if things are too small or too big or have pictures ready.
That's a pro tip. And don't be afraid to size up. If you're not sure, with Asian sizing
it's always better to go with bigger size. This is designed to never trust the letter
on the label when ordering Asian clothing and I mean does it look like I'm wearing extra large?
No it doesn't. Do I care that it's an extra large? No I don't because I know that it's a good fit
in this way and you wouldn't know if I wouldn't have told you.
I also really like the black one more than the white and blue one obviously because that's just
my personal favorite color black anyway have you ever been humbled by Asian
sizing tell me your story in the comments down below also check out the
description text because I link the Amorese shop there put down my discount
code put down my other socials and yeah please leave a thumbs up to this video
consider subscribing to my channel I will see you in the next video have a
nice day bye